anyone in computing the availability of
storage space is no longer the issue it
once was with the advent of online
storage in the cloud larger hard drives
shared network drives and large capacity
memory sticks the transfer and saving of
data can be done fast and efficiently
and file size no longer seems to be the
issue however there may still be
instances where you need to compress a
file for instance you need to send it as
an attachment to an email where there is
a limit or maybe a kiyosaki internet
connection is slow of a network
connection is slow and the smaller the
file size the quicker it can be sent to
compress a file or folder you simply
need a selector for all I'll fail and
I'm going to use it IT cost rollers an
example for this so if I right click on
the folder and then select from the
drop-down compressed zipped folder and
click on that it will create an exact
duplicate of the IT course folder
however it has been compressed as can be
identified with this hip down the flora
as you can see the size of this file is
no 417 kilobytes as opposed to 715
kilobytes of so it has nearly half tin
size